[Joe] Well, hello there.
你好
Who are you?
你是谁？
Based on your vibe, a student.
看你的样子是个学生
Your blouse is loose.
你穿着宽松的衬衫
You're not here to be ogled, but those bracelets, they jangle.
你不是来引人注意的 但那些手镯叮当作响
You like a little attention.
你想要些许关注
Okay, I bite.
好吧 你引起了我的兴趣
You search the books. Fiction, "F" through "K."
你在找书 找小说 首字母从“F”到“K”
Now...
好了…
Hmm, you're not the standard insecure nymph
你不是那种标准的找福克纳的书 却永远读不到最后的没安全感的女生
Too sun-kissed for Stephen King.
健康的肤色说明 你也不读斯蒂芬金的书
Who will you buy?
你会买谁的书呢？
[Beck gasps] Sorry.
对不起
[Joe] You sound apologetic, like you're embarrassed to be a good girl,
你听上去很抱歉 好像你为当一个好姑娘而尴尬
and you murmur your first word to me.
你低声对我说了第一个词
Hello.
你好
Do you work here?
你在这里工作吗？
Guilty.
没错
-Can I help you find something? -Paula Fox.
-你要找什么吗？ -宝拉福克斯的书
It's a good choice.
挺有眼光
She's gonna be in here.
她的书在这里
"Celebrity authors"? I thought Fox was pretty obscure.
“知名作家”？ 我以为福克斯没什么名气呢
She is Courtney Love's maternal grandmother.
她是科特妮洛芙的外婆
You're not expected to know that.
你应该不知道
Good. I didn't.
很好 我不知道
Mr. Mooney wants anyone in here who's even tangentially famous.
穆尼先生想把哪怕只有一点出名的 作者的书都放在这里
He thinks it sells more books.
他觉得这样能卖出更多的书
That's sad.
真可悲
People buying books because of what's popular,
人们看什么书流行就买什么书
and not because they wanna be moved or changed in some way.
而不是因为他们想在某些方面 被感动或是被改变
Yeah. It's an epidemic.
对 是有这种风气
Yeah, you see this guy? Here, the glasses, behind you.
嗯 你看到这家伙了吗？ 这个 你身后戴眼镜的这个
He just grabbed Dan Brown's latest on the way in.
他刚刚进来时拿了丹布朗最新的小说
So he's gonna wander around for another, like, five or ten minutes,
所以他会再转上五或十分钟
just to find something legitimate to buy with it.
去找一本能装装样子的书一并买下
Oh, like the cereal guys buy when they're really there for condoms.
就像那些买麦片的人 其实是去买安全套的
Only makes it more conspicuous. Like, own your shit.
那只会更明显 还不如敢做敢当
If Dan Brown's your kink, then be out about it.
如果丹布朗就是你的心头爱 就坦荡承认吧
Sometimes they surprise you.
有时候他们会让你惊讶
-Paula Fox. Top shelf. You want me to... -Oh, no, I got it.
-宝拉福克斯 在最顶层 需要我… -不 我能够到
[Joe] Oh. Are you not wearing a bra?
你没穿胸罩吗？
And you want me to notice.
你想让我注意到
If this was a movie,
如果是在拍电影
I'd grab you and we'd go at it right in the stacks.
我会一把抓住你 然后我们会在书堆里做爱
Have you read her fiction? Desperate Characters, it's her best.
你读过她的小说吗？ 《绝望的人们》 那是她最棒的作品
[sighs] That's what I keep hearing.
我一直听说那本书
-You haven't read Desperate Characters? -I know. I know.
-你没读过《绝望的人们》？ -我知道
I'm worried it's not gonna live up to the hype.
我担心那书名不符实
I can safely say it is that good.
我可以打保票那书跟大家说的一样好
That's a high endorsement. And from a bookstore clerk, nonetheless.
这真是很高的认可 虽然是书店工作人员口中说出来的
Well, it's bookstore manager.
是书店经理
Hello? Anyone working here?
喂？这里有工作人员吗？
-Asshole. -Mmm...
混蛋
Do you mind? Uh, I'm in a hurry.
能快点吗？我很着急
[Joe] He's just pissed he's gotta buy Salinger to feel respectable
他很生气要买本塞林格的书 让自己觉得被尊重
when all he really wants to do is eat Cheetos and jerk it to iPorn
而其实他真正想做的是吃奇多 在苹果设备上看黄片手淫
before washing it all down with a Dan Brown chaser.
然后再读完丹布朗的书
Have a nice day, sir.
祝您今天愉快 先生
Okay, I'm going for it.
好了 我决定买这本
-Good. You won't regret it. -I'd better not.
-好极了 你不会后悔的 -最好不会
Paula Fox. Nice.
宝拉福克斯 不错
You know, she was, uh, Courtney Love's maternal grandmother.
她是科特妮洛芙的外婆
That's why I'm buying it.
所以我才买的
[Joe] You have enough cash to cover this, but you want me to know your name.
你有足够的现金付账 但你想让我知道你的名字
-"Guinevere"? -Yeah.
-“吉娜薇”？ -是的
My parents were assholes with the whole naming thing.
我父母太不会取名了
But everyone just calls me Beck.
但大家都叫我贝可
And you're Joe...
你叫乔伊…
Goldberg.
戈登伯格
Everyone calls me Joe.
大家都叫我乔伊
Aren't you gonna tell me to have a nice day?
你不祝我今天愉快吗？
You have a nice day, Beck.
祝你今天愉快 贝可
You have one yourself, Joe.
也祝你今天愉快 乔伊
[Joe] You smiled, laughed at my jokes,
你对我微笑 为我说的笑话发笑
told me your name, asked for mine.
告诉了我你的名字 问了我的名字
She write her number on there? She was on you hard.
她在上面写她的号码了吗？ 她对你有意思
No, she was just being nice.
不 她只是很友好
I'd be googling the hell out of her right now.
我会立刻去谷歌上搜索她的全部信息
You know her full name.
你知道她的全名了
That's pretty aggressive, Ethan.
那也太积极了 伊森
What do I tell you? Always be closing that shit.
我怎么跟你说的？一定要主动出击
[both] If you need me, I'll be in cookbooks.
你需要我的话 我就在烹饪书那一块
But for work. Not for fun. I swear.
但我是去工作 不是去玩的 我发誓
[Joe] At the end of the day, people are really just disappointing, aren't they?
最后 人们真让人失望 对吗？
But are you, Beck? Are you?
但你是吗 贝可？你是吗？
Yes, people find "the one."
是 人们寻找“命中注定的那个人”
I believe that. I try to stay open.
我相信 我努力做到思想开明
I was in love once. She broke my heart, Beck.
我也曾恋爱过 她让我心碎了 贝可
Ugh, she really did a number on me.
她真的伤透了我的心
I should've seen the signs.
我应该看到那些迹象的
But we never do when we're in love.
但我们在恋爱的时候永远看不到
-Exhibit A. Claudia and Ron. -[indistinct arguing]
例子一 克劳迪亚跟罗恩
[Ron] I went out for a couple of drinks. Get off my back.
我出去喝了几杯 别追问了
[Joe] Claudia's a nurse. Single parent.
克劳迪亚是个护士 单身母亲
[Claudia] Leave me alone! You're on your phone...
别烦我！你在打电话…
[Joe] You think she knew Ron was a shitbag when she fell in love?
你觉得她恋爱的时候 知道罗恩是个混蛋吗？
No, she thought he was a prince.
不 她那时觉得他是个王子
Hey, Paco.
嘿 帕克
'Sup, Joe?
你好吗 乔伊？
[Joe] And now,
现在
-hers is not the only life she ruined. -[Claudia] Leave me alone!
-她毁掉的不仅是自己的人生 -别烦我！
Why is coming home such a chore for you? [continues indistinctly]
为什么回家这么让你心烦？
Is everything cool in there?
没事吧？
Yeah, Mom and Ron are just talking.
-没事 妈妈和罗恩只是在说话 -你总是跟你的朋友出去鬼混！
-And I'm sick of it! -Wow.
-我受够了！ -哇噢
You are burning through that book, aren't you?
那本书你快看完了 是吗？
Reads quick. It's good.
我读得很快 很好看
[Claudia] Screw you, Ron! Get out of here! Leave me alone.
去你的 罗恩！滚出去！别烦我
Are you hungry?
你饿吗？
'Cause, you know, I just got this meatball sub,
因为我买了这个肉丸三明治
but I remembered I have Thai from last night.
但我想到还有些昨晚剩下的泰国菜
Nah. My mom will just make me something later.
不了 我妈妈晚点会给我做饭的
That's a shame. This won't keep. It's getting tossed.
真可惜 这个不能放 要被扔掉了
You sure, Joe?
你确定吗 乔伊？
"All for one and one for all."
“人人为我 我为人人”
[Joe] The point, Beck... Love is, uh, tricky.
问题是 贝可…爱是很微妙的
[Joe] A guy needs to protect himself.
人需要保护自己
I had to be sure you're safe.
我得确定你是个安全的人
And your name was a glorious place to start.
从你的名字开始是最好的
Not a lot of Guinevere Becks.
没多少人叫吉娜薇贝可
And there you were. Every account set to public.
找到你了 所有的账号都对公众可见
You want to be seen, heard, known.
你想要被看见、被听见、被人了解
Of course, I obliged.
当然 我照做了
Born and raised, Nantucket Island.
出生并成长于南塔克特岛
A brother, Clyde, and sister, Anya.
有个兄弟叫克莱德 一个姐妹叫安雅
Your parents really were assholes about the names.
你的父母真是不会取名
Your folks split when you were 12. Your dad dropped out of the picture.
你12岁的时候父母离异 你的父亲从此了无音讯
Went to Brown where you majored in lit. Cool.
你上了布朗大学 专业是文学 酷
And minored in douchebags. Hmm.
辅修人渣课程
And then on to NYC to conquer an MFA and make your mark, presumably.
然后去了纽约市攻读艺术硕士 大概想要成就一番名气吧
Now you still write. Barely.
你现在还在写作 写得很少
Too busy living out moments you won't remember five years from now.
太忙碌于过你五年之后 都不会记得的生活了
I know this because you post about this life all the goddamn time.
我知道 因为你一直 在发布这种生活的点滴
[Joe] Candidly, it's the least appealing thing about you, Beck.
老实说 这是你最没吸引力的部分了 贝可
You posted this hours after our encounter.
你在我们相遇几小时后发布了这个
[Joe] I was concerned you didn't mention that cute guy in a bookstore.
没有提到书店里 那个可爱的家伙 让我担心
And then I realized your online life isn't real.
然后我意识到你的网上人生并不真实
It's a collage.
这是个…拼贴画
You paste this Beck up. This...
你拼贴出了这个贝可的生活 这个…
together, lovable, cute, bendy little creature.
自信、讨喜、可爱、柔韧的小可人
If anything, the fact that you didn't share me with your followers
如果有什么的话 你没有把我 分享给你的订阅者这件事
only confirms we really connected.
只证实了我们真的有联系
The next thing our little friend the Internet gave me was your address.
接着我在网上找到了你的地址
There it is, with its big, naked windows.
就是这里 有着无遮挡的大窗户
It's nice. Too nice.
挺好 太好了
I'm thinking subsidized school housing.
我想这是拿补贴的校舍
Jesus! It's like you've never seen a horror movie or the news.
天啊！你好像从来没看过恐怖电影 或是新闻
But you want people to watch, don't you?
但你想让人们看你 不是吗？
You know, I plan on asking you about this quality
我计划等我们熟悉之后
when we get to know each other better.
问问关于你这项特质的问题
A proposal.
一个提议
Why don't we spend the day together tomorrow?
不如我们明天一起共度吧？
Just you and me?
只有你跟我？
And in the meantime, mac and cheese!
“同时 享受芝士通心粉吧！”
[Joe] It's cute. Not deep. But cute. Is there more to you? Let's find out.
很可爱 没深度 但可爱 你还有更多面吗？让我们发现一下吧
Our day starts at the ass-crack of dawn.
天一破晓 我们的一天就开始了
I know from your posted schedule that you teach a 6:30 class
我从你发布的日程表了解到 你6点半要去教一堂
called Get Up N Flow.
被称为“起来运动”的课
You caress the sweaty backs of bulimic, dead-eyed real mommies of SoHo...
你温柔地触碰那些来自苏荷区 双眼无神的肥胖妈妈们汗湿的背部…
I am loving your form today, Tasha.
我喜欢你今天的线条 塔莎
[Joe] ...offering smiles and lies of encouragement.
…微笑着说着客套的鼓励的话
[Joe] By 10:00, you're at campus to TA a Romantics class
到了10点 你在大学的 浪漫主义课程上当助教
and play Vanna White to some shirt.
给某个教授当助手
Morning, Professor Leahy.
早上好 莱西教授
I told you, it's Paul. Are you ready for class?
我跟你说过了叫我保罗 你准备好上课了吗？
[Joe] Professor Obvious wants to fuck you.
教授显然想上你
Now, you're smart. You let him think one day he might.
你很聪明 你让他以为 有一天他会有机会
And what's the harm in that, right?
这样又有什么损失呢 对吧？
After class, you head to your favorite café
下课后 你去你最喜欢的咖啡馆
to write for the first time all day.
进行一整天第一次的写作
But your life doesn't cooperate.
但你的生活并不如你所愿
Your wealthy girlfriends have just now woken up,
你有钱的女友们才刚睡醒
and have nothing better to do
除了策划下一个
than plan their next pointless yet instagrammable night.
可以在社交软件上发布的无聊夜生活 就没有什么好做的了
Can we get real for a second?
我们能现实一点吗？
You have questionable taste in friends, Beck.
你交友的品味有问题 贝可
-[all] Cheers! -Yeah!
-干杯！ -耶！
-Oh, yes. Happy birthday! -[Annika laughs] Thank you so much.
-对了 生日快乐！ -太感谢了
[Joe] And expensive taste in lives.
生活中买的东西太昂贵了
-Ready? -Thank you.
-准备好了吗？ -谢谢
No, I hate it. Of course I love it!
不 我不喜欢 我当然喜欢了！
Jason didn't even get her something that nice,
杰森都不给她买那么好的内衣
and Annika finally let him do anal.
安妮卡最后就让他爆菊了
-[Lynn] Oh, my God! -Please, please, it was time.
-我的天！ -拜托 那是时候到了
Please open my gift next and tell me how much you hate me then, lady.
接下来请打开我的礼物 告诉我你有多讨厌我 姑娘
A butterfly? It's my spirit animal for the year. You remembered?
一只蝴蝶？ 这是我的年度灵兽 你记得？
Only 'cause you wouldn't shut up about it.
只是因为你一直喋喋不休地提到它
[Joe] You want so badly to be one of them.
你非常想要融入她们
-[Beck] Happy birthday. -[Annika] You look so beautiful.
-生日快乐 -你看起来真漂亮
[Joe] Well, they've got nothing to do after this.
她们之后就无事可做了
So, yeah, they'll party till 5:00 and scrape it together tomorrow.
对 她们会开派对直到凌晨5点 然后明天再一起聚会
But you can't. You have to work for a living.
但你不行 你得要为谋生而工作
A McQueen, Beck? How much was it?
麦昆牌的 贝可？多少钱？
[chuckles] It was on clearance.
是清仓商品
They haven't put a McQueen scarf on clearance
麦昆2010年上吊后
since he hung himself in 2010.
围巾就没有清仓出售过了
It'd be too much even if she did deserve it,
就算她值得也太贵了
which she does not.
何况她不值得
[Peach] You always do this.
你总是这样
You make, like, a big gesture that you can't afford because...
你大手笔地买 你买不起的东西 因为…
How broke are you?
你有多缺钱？
Just tell me what's up.
告诉我怎么回事
[Joe] Actually sounds like she cares.
听上去她其实很在乎你
[Beck] Look, I appreciate--
听着 我很感激…
[Peach] Why don't you just let me loan you some cash?
你为什么不让我借你点现金呢？
Okay? I keep telling you, it's nothing.
好吗？我一直跟你说 这没什么
[Joe] Also, sounds condescending.
同时 听上去还很居高临下
You know I'd do anything for you. Don't forget that.
你知道我愿意为你做一切事情 别忘记了
-Sure you can't come out with us? -I gotta write.
-确定不跟我们出去玩吗？ -我得写作
Virtuous. Catch you later?
好姑娘 晚点聊吧？
[Joe] Is that the best friend you've got?
那是你最好的朋友了吗？
If so, Beck, you really are alone.
如果是的话 贝可 你真的很孤独
Your social media's a liar.
你的社交媒体编造出了一个谎言
It says you're a happy-go-lucky dilettante.
你在上面表现成 一个逍遥自在的业余文学爱好者
But, underneath it all, you seem like the genuine article.
但在一切表象之下 你似乎是有真材实料的
Stretched ADD thin, sure, but as soon as the door closes...
注意力缺失 当然 但一旦关上门…
you're back at the keyboard, trying to write.
你又回到了键盘前 想要努力写作
[man] Thanks.
谢谢
Keep the change, man.
不用找了 伙计
Hey. Let me up.
嘿 让我上去
My best friend walked in on you getting your dick sucked
我最好的朋友看到 你在我带你去的派对上
by some random woman in a bathroom at a party that I took you to!
在洗手间里 让一个陌生女人帮你口交！
I was wasted. I didn't even finish.
我喝醉了 我都没射精
That's your apology? "I didn't cum." That's the one you're going with?
你就这么道歉？“我没到高潮” 那是你要说的话吗？
I obviously shouldn't have gone in the bathroom
我显然不应该跟除你之外的
with any girl that wasn't you.
任何女孩去洗手间
But she said she had good coke, and I'd been seriously stressed.
但她说她有上好的可卡因 我压力一直非常大
I thought, when Johno and I started our line,
我跟乔诺开始做这行时
it was gonna be like picking out flavors and shit.
我以为就会是挑选一下口味之类的
It turns out it's 16-hour lectures on microbial management.
结果是16个小时 关于微生物管理的演讲
And that's why no one starts their own artisanal soda company,
那就是为什么没有人 开自己的手工汽水公司
and why America has to keep drinking crap that's giving 'em cancer.
还有为什么美国人 一直得喝让自己得癌症的垃圾
You actually managed to connect your illicit blowjob to curing cancer.
你竟然把你的口交外遇 跟治愈癌症联系起来了
I'm genuinely impressed.
真是了不起
Beck, I...
贝可 我…
Seriously, I am drowning in work.
讲真的 我现在工作很忙
I don't have time to keep hooking up or whatever it is you're even capable of.
我没时间一直跟你乱搞 或是做什么你擅长的事
I know I've done some stupid shit, but I'm on it now.
我知道我做了些蠢事 但我现在改了
I don't wanna be just some guy you sleep with.
我不想只跟你上床而已
[whispering] God, you make me insane.
天啊 你让我疯狂了
[Joe] Way to go, Beck. Looks like a catch.
厉害了 贝可 看上去真是个理想对象
Benjamin J. Ashby III. Oh, there's three of them.
本杰明J阿什比三世 有三个同名的
Greenwich-born, boarding-school bred.
出生在格林威治 上的是寄宿学校
His father is the Ben Ashby of Ashby Brokerage.
他的爸爸是阿什比经纪行的本阿什比
Two failed careers. Model. Oh, boy.
做过两份失败的工作 模特 天啊
And co-creator of a dating app
还有一个约会软件的联合创始人
that connects people through musical tastes called LoveHooks.
是一个通过音乐品味把人 关联起来的软件 叫做“恋爱交友”
Current CEO of Home Soda Artisanal Beverages.
现在是手工饮料家庭汽水的 首席执行官
Motto...
座右铭…
"Drink better by hand," which makes no sense,
“用手喝更好” 这话毫无意义
but evokes a homespun quality
但放在一个穿着价值六百美元
that lines up with a guy who wears $600 Japanese sneakers.
日本运动鞋的家伙身上 有种朴素的感觉
The hair, the privilege he tries to hide with retweets of Black Lives Matter.
发型、他想要通过转发“黑人的命 也是命”的推文隐藏的特权
Not to sound judgey, but this guy is everything wrong with America.
不想听上去像是批判别人 但这家伙就跟美国精神完全格格不入
See, this is why I do my research.
所以我要调查
You fall for the wrong men.
你爱上了错的人
Bad men.
坏男人们
You let them in. You let them hurt you.
你让他们进你家 你让他们伤害你
Too far away to know for sure, but my guess is,
还不能确定 但我猜
if he came anywhere close to making you cum,
要是他有一点可能让你高潮
you would've made a Broadway show out of it.
你就会做出百老汇水平的表演
But you didn't, 'cause he didn't.
但你没有 因为他没那能耐
-"Desperate Characters." -Yeah, I just got it.
-《绝望的人们》 -是的 我刚买的
Borrow it when I'm done. It's supposed to be her best.
我读完了可以借给你 这应该是她写得最好的一部
Johno's consultant we brought in,
我们请的乔诺的顾问
she's been all over me about this kind of thing.
她一直在跟我说这种东西
Saged the crap out of the office.
烧些东西让办公室充满正能量
The book title has the word "desperate" in it.
书名里有“绝望”两字
You don't want to think of yourself as a desperate character, Beck.
但你别觉得自己是个绝望的人 贝可
Because you're the opposite, babe.
因为你正相反 宝贝
You're the smartest girl I know.
你是我认识最聪明的姑娘
Honestly, you blow me away.
老实说 我为你着迷
Oh, shit. Gotta roll. Johno's blowing up my phone.
该死 该走了 乔诺一直在给我打电话
Hey, you should come by the office, test out some new flavors.
嘿 你应该来办公室试尝一些新口味
We're doing cumin. I know how much you like Indian food.
我们开发出了孜然口味 我知道你有多喜欢印度菜
Sure. Sounds good.
当然好 听上去很好
It looks good on you, by the way.
另外 你胖了点
The extra weight.
看上去不错
Yeah. Hey. I'm on my way, bro.
对 嘿 我来了 兄弟
You guys ordering pizzas?
你们点了批萨？
Yeah, don't dick me over like last time. Gluten-free crust.
对 别像上次那样坑我了 要不含麸质的脆皮
Not from that vegan place. Vegan cheese tastes like asshole.
别从那家素食店订 素食芝士吃起来跟屎一样
[Benji] I'm talking French gourmet shit.
我说的是法国美食
No. Johno. Johno. Listen to me.
不 乔诺 听我说
They can't do half-gluten-free 'cause it's dough.
他们做不了一半不含麸质的 因为那是生面团
They have to use a spelt dough.
他们得用斯佩尔特小麦粉做的面团
[Joe] So you didn't finish.
所以你还没满足
Just like that.
就这样
Thank you. You're so kind. [chuckles]
谢谢 你真好
I don't suppose you can help me get a cab, can you?
你能帮我叫辆出租车吗？
Of course.
当然可以
-Thanks. -Yeah.
-谢谢 -嗯
Wow. Don't tell me you're finished already.
哇噢 别告诉我说你已经读完了
Almost.
差不多了
It's so good.
太好看了
Sometimes the dialogue's weird, though.
但有时候对话很奇怪
Like when they're killing each other and still all nice about it.
像是他们要杀掉彼此的时候 还很客气
Well, it was the 19th century. People still had manners.
那是19世纪 人们还是很礼貌的
I was hoping we could go get another one.
我希望我们能去再拿一本
I want you to cum...
我想让你高潮…
[Joe] Something's in the air tonight, Beck,
今晚很有气氛 贝可 因为除了我之外的所有人都在做爱
Even the lovebirds made up.
就连爱情鸟都在交配
Yeah. Yeah, why not? Sure.
嗯 为什么不去呢？当然要去了
[Paco] Did you know Dumas was a black dude? I googled him.
你知道仲马是个黑人吗？ 我上谷歌搜索他了
His grandmother was a slave, and his dad was a brigadier general.
他的祖母是个奴隶 他的父亲是个准将
He killed like half a battalion.
他杀了半个营的人
You probably knew that since you work at a bookstore.
你在书店工作 可能已经知道了
I didn't.
我不知道
-How'd you get to work here, anyway? -Mr. Mooney gave me a job
-你怎么会在这里工作呢？ -在我比你大一点的年纪时
when I was just a little older than you. He sort of took me in.
穆尼先生给了我这份工作 他像是收留了我
-He seems nice. -He's a dick.
-他似乎是个好人 -他是个混蛋
But he loved books, and he taught me to love them, too.
但他爱书 他也教会了我爱书
I never see him around here.
我从没见他来过这里
-Is he dead? -No. He's just old.
-他死了吗？ -不 他只是老了
I'm sorry, Pac.
对不起 帕克
I had one back here for you, but Ethan must've sold it.
我留了一本给你的 但伊森一定卖掉了
-Sold what? -Your next read.
-卖了什么？ -你下一本要读的书
Come on. I'll show you where we keep the good stuff.
来吧 我让你看看我们放好书的地方
[Paco] Freaky.
真奇特
It's the Cage.
这是个笼子
It's where we keep early editions and collectibles.
是我们放早期版本跟收藏的地方
It's cold.
很冷
Sixty-five degrees. For the books.
18度 用于保存书籍的
If the zombies come, this is where I'm hiding.
要是僵尸来了 我要藏在这里
Why don't you set that milkshake down?
不如把那杯奶昔放下吧？
[Mooney] Careful, Joseph.
小心 约瑟夫
When it comes to the value of a book, it's all about condition. I'll show you.
书的价值完全在于其保存状态 我来告诉你
[Joe] It's always 65 degrees.
温度一直是18度
Humidity 40%. Too moist, the pages can mildew...
40%的湿度 太潮的话 书页会发霉…
[Mooney] Too dry, they get brittle.
太干的话就会变脆
Always keep books upright
一直要让书直立
so the spines don't become rolled or warped or what we call "cocked."
书脊就不会卷起来或是变弯 或是我们说的“翘起来”
And we never wanna fold or crease the pages.
永远不要折书页
And we dust the covers with a chemical-free duster.
用不含化学成分的抹布 拂去封面的灰尘
Always towards the spine.
拿的时候一直拿书脊柱
Under no circumstances is there any sunlight in this room.
这间屋子里不能进阳光
Sunlight can ruin a book as fast as fire.
阳光会像火一样快地把书给毁掉
Faster.
比火更快
That's a lot of stuff to remember just to take care of some old books.
为了保存好一些老书 要记的东西真多
The most valuable things in life are usually...
生活中最有价值的东西通常是…
the most helpless.
最无助的
So they need people like us to protect them. You know?
所以需要像我们一样的人 去保护它们 知道吗？
"Don Quicks-oat."
“堂肯德鸡”
Quixote. It's about a guy who believes in chivalry,
是吉诃德 说的是一个信奉骑士精神的人
so he decides to be an old-school knight.
他决定当一个老派的骑士
What's chivalry?
什么是骑士精神？
It's treating people with respect. Especially women. Like men should.
是用尊敬的态度对待别人 特别是女人 像男人们应该做的那样
It's good. It's one of my favorites.
是本好书 是我最爱的书之一
I probably shouldn't take this home.
我可能不应该拿这本回家
It's not a first edition, it's just an old one.
这不是第一版 只是旧版
Besides, I trust you.
再说了 我信任你
-Where you been, Paco? -We just grabbed some milkshakes.
-你去哪了 帕克？ -我们只是去买奶昔了
-You just walk off with strangers? -Joe's not a stranger.
-你刚跟陌生人走了？ -乔伊不是陌生人
Yes, he is.
是 他是
Inside. Now. Okay?
快进去 好吗？
Keep away from my girlfriend's kid.
离我女朋友的孩子远点
Look, I'm sorry, but he was out here, and he could hear everything in there.
对不起 但他刚刚在外面 让他听到你们在里面的动静不大好吧
Don't you tell me how to parent.
别教我怎么养育孩子
This whole nice guy act might work on other people.
这套装好人的行为 在其他人身上可能管用
I'm a parole officer, 15 years, and I can see what you are.
我当假释官当了15年 我能看出你是什么货色
[Joe] Well, you're an alcoholic shitbag who beats women.
你是个打女人的酒鬼
So, please, enlighten me.
所以拜托来开导我吧
You're a freak.
你是个怪胎
So, stay away from Paco, because if you don't,
离帕克远点 不然的话
I'll grab a steak knife and I'll cut those freak eyes out.
我会拿把牛排刀把你的眼睛挖出来
[Joe] There are scary people in the world, Beck.
世界上有可怕的人 贝可
That's why it's important to be safe.
所以保证安全很重要
And why I have to do what I'm about to do.
以及为什么我要做我将要做的事
Fun fact.
有趣的事情
Did you know the law requires gas leaks to be investigated?
你知道法律要求要调查煤气泄漏吗？
I've been learning a lot since I met you.
我见到你之后学到了很多
Hey, Beck? You left the door open again.
嘿 贝可？你又没关门
I thought we said we weren't gonna do that anymore.
我以为我们说好了 不会再发生这种事了
I was careful to call the gas company on a day when you had a full schedule.
我很小心地在你一整天都有事的时候 打给了煤气公司
I wouldn't wanna scare you.
我不想吓到你
Hey. Is Beck here?
嘿 贝可在家吗？
Nope. Super let me in. Someone reported a leak.
不在 管理员让我进来的 有人说这里有煤气泄漏
Right. Yeah. She mentioned that. Is everything okay?
对 嗯 她提到过 没事吧？
Yeah, all clear. Tell your girlfriend there's no leak.
对 没问题 告诉你女朋友没有泄漏
I'm done, so...
我弄完了 所以…
Okay. Thanks. Well, I can just lock up.
好的 谢谢 我来锁门
I just need to know who you really are.
我只是需要知道你到底是什么样的人
Besides a broke poetry student
除了是一个住在
in a subsidized apartment you could never afford.
你永远租不起的校舍里 写诗的穷学生外
Where is it, Beck?
在哪里 贝可？
When we live together, your place won't be a pigsty.
我们住在一起后 你家就不会像个猪窝了
I'll clean for us.
我可以打扫
And you won't eat all this frozen shit. I'll cook for you every day. I promise.
你不会吃这些速冻垃圾食品了 我每天都会为你下厨 我保证
I'll even do your laundry.
我甚至会帮你洗衣服
And take care of your favorite books.
呵护你最爱的书
I'll make our bed every morning.
我每天早上都会整理床单
And no matter how hard you fight me,
不管你多抗拒我
I will always make sure you password protect your devices.
我都永远会确保 你的密码能保护你的电脑
[Leahy] "One day You won't need love anymore
“一天 你将不再需要爱
One day, you won't walk through the world
一天 你将不再在这世界上行走
As though it was your job To hold everything up
好像让一切停下是你的工作
The sun, the sky The hard part of the night"
太阳、天空 黑夜里最难的部分”
It's good.
很棒
It's quite good.
非常棒
But, Beck, where's the rest? You owe me 20 more pages.
但是贝可 其它的呢？ 你还欠我20页
If the schedule is too rigorous, drop back to part-time.
如果时间安排不过来 就做回兼职生吧
But then I won't qualify to TA.
那我就不够资格当助教了
I need the cash. The housing. I'd lose my place.
我需要现金付房租 我会无家可归的
You'll figure it out. You're smart, or you wouldn't be here.
你会搞定的 你很聪明 不然你就不会到这里来了
-Please, Professor Leahy-- -Paul.
-拜托 莱西教授… -叫我保罗
Paul. I'll get you the pages by the end of the week.
保罗 我会在这周结束前 把文稿给您的
I can't go to part-time, okay?
我不能做兼职 好吗？
You just need to keep up.
你需要加把劲
Happy to discuss further. After class some evening.
很乐意跟你进一步讨论一下 找一天放学之后的晚上
If we're gonna seriously discuss poetry, it should be over a drink.
如果我们要认真讨论诗歌 就应该边喝边聊
There's a little gastropub I love...
有一家我很喜欢的美食酒吧…
I would love that, Paul. [chuckles]
我很愿意去 保罗
Just, uh, how would your wife feel about you--
只是 你的妻子会有什么感觉…
About me helping out an aspiring writer? She's used to my generosity.
关于我帮助一个有抱负的作家吗？ 她很明白 我一向这么慷慨
[Leahy] So, Thursday night, then?
那就周四晚上吧？
Thursday night it is.
就周四晚上吧
Excellent.
好极了
And don't worry about the next few days. Just go home and get caught up.
别为接下来几天担心 回家准备吧
[Beck] Need to see you tonight.
“今晚需要见你”
[Benji] Will if I can, babe. Working late.
“如果可以的话 宝贝 我会工作到很晚”
P.S., I can still smell you on my fingers.
“另外 我还是能在手指上 闻到你的味道”
[Joe] I learned two definitive things by scouring your computer.
通过彻底查看你的电脑 我知道了两样决定性的事情
First, there are no recent pictures of your dad because he's dead.
首先 没有看到你父亲的近照 因为他死了
He OD'd and you were the one that found him.
他吸毒过量 是你发现了他的尸体
You've started a few poems about that day, but you never finished them.
你开始写了几首关于那天的诗 但你一直没有写完
I'm so sorry, Beck.
我很抱歉 贝可
But none of this matters because of my second and greatest discovery.
但这一切都不重要 因为我有了第二个最重要的发现
11:06 a.m., an hour after our encounter at the bookstore,
上午11点06分 我们在书店相遇的一个小时后
amidst a group text on the merits of vaginal detoxing, you wrote...
在一次讨论用草药蒸法 清洁阴道的好处的群聊中 你写道…
[Beck] Wow. Just met a human male who actually reads.
“哇 刚遇到了一个 真正会阅读的男人”
Alert the media.
“大家注意”
What if it's finally time for me to date someone good for me?
“也许我终于是时候 要跟适合我的人约会了？”
[Joe] Thank you for letting me know
谢谢你让我知道我并不是疯了
[Joe] No!
不！
Yes, I remember what you said when you sent money last.
对 我记得你上次寄钱来时说过什么
Yes, I'm grateful.
对 我很感激
I did. He basically offered to sleep with me.
我有 他基本上是提议让我跟他上床
No, I can't report him. That's not how it works.
不 我不能举报他 不能那样
[Joe] I'm not worried. I've seen enough romantic comedies
我不担心 我看过足够多的爱情喜剧
to know guys like me are always getting in jams like this.
知道像我这样的家伙 总是会陷入这种窘境
Not the school, the world. That's not how the world works.
不是学校 是社会 社会不是这样混的
I know how much you helped me, it's just... It's hard here, Mom.
我知道你帮了我多少 只是… 我处境很困难 妈妈
Okay. I'll figure it out.
好吧 我会搞定的
All right. Love you, too.
好了 我也爱你
Bye, Mom.
再见 妈妈
[Joe] It's okay, Beck.
没事的 贝可
Hi, Becks.
嗨 贝可
Hey, bitch, where you at? Come play!
嘿 贱人 你在哪？来玩吧！
I can't. I just had the worst day.
我不能去 今天是我最糟糕的一天
there's nothing that we can't fix, okay?
没什么我们解决不了的 好吗？
Yes, us and copious amounts of alcohol.
-对 我们还有很多酒 -我的天 有打折！
-You guys love me? -[Peach] Of course.
-你们爱我吗？ -当然爱了
-[Lynn] Why would you even say that? -[Beck] Okay, then.
-你怎么会说这种话呢？ -那好吧
Meet me in Greenpoint.
到绿点见面吧
Look, why don't you come here? Okay? Come here.
听着 不如你过来吧？好吗？过来
[Lynn] It's actually really fun where we are.
-我们在的地方其实很好玩 -不行
-No. -[Lynn] I promise.
-我保证 -对
There's something I need to do for myself.
我有些要为自己做的事
I'll text you on my way.
我在路上给你们发短信
See you soon.
一会儿见
-Bye!
-再见！
[sighs] Fuck!
该死！
[Joe] I guess we're going to Greenpoint, Beck.
我想我们要去绿点了 贝可
I never go to Greenpoint.
我从没去过绿点
But the things you do for love, right?
但为爱会做傻事 对吗？
[Beck] Hi. Um, okay, we're gonna get a few more drinks.
嗨 好 我们再来几杯
Hold on, one second.
等等 等一下
Guys?
各位？
[Peach] What is she thinking?
她在想什么？
Open mics are for models-slash- singer-songwriters-slash-vegans.
开放麦克风是为模特兼歌手 兼歌曲作家兼素食主义者准备的
These people don't want to hear
这些人不想听
some wannabe read a poem about the bleakness of life or whatever.
某个想要成功的人 读什么关于凄惨生活的诗之类的
[Joe] Your friends are disloyal. And that Peach is the worst.
你的朋友不靠谱 那个皮琪是最不靠谱的
Beckish, do we think now's the night?
贝可宝贝 要挑今晚吗？
Positive.
是的
All of my life lately has been about surviving.
我最近的生活都是在挣扎求生
I need to remind myself why I came here in the first place.
我需要提醒自己我最初来这里的原因
-Yes. -Yeah.
-对
-You go. So good. -Who do you keep texting?
-去吧 好耶 -你一直在给谁发短信？
I invited Benji.
我邀请了本吉
-Beck... -What? He likes poetry.
-贝可… -什么？他喜欢诗
-For sure. -And he texted he was coming?
-当然 -他发短信说他要来？
He texted a row of smile emojis, like, 45 minutes ago.
他差不多45分钟前 发了一串微笑的表情
Some guys are assholes, and you just have to realize that.
有些男人就是混蛋 你得明白这点
I get it, Peach.
我知道 皮琪
You're the one who told me to keep reminding you he's a bastard.
是你跟我说要一直提醒你 他是个王八蛋的
Up next, we have Guinevere Beck.
接下来有请吉娜薇贝可
-All right.
-好了
To vulnerability and shit!
敬脆弱和欺骗！
[Lynn] Yeah.
对
-Cheers. -Okay.
-干杯 -好的
[Annika] Kill it, Beck!
好好表现 贝可！
Hey, everyone. Um, I'm Beck, and I'm... [chuckles]
嗨 各位 我是贝可 我是个…
Not to sound like, you know, whatever, but just...
不想听上去好像 随便吧 但…
I'm a poet.
我是个诗人
Yeah, you are!
对 你是！
"One day, you won't need love anymore
“一天 你将不再需要爱
One day, you won't walk through the world
一天 你将不再在这世界上行走
As though it was your job To hold everything up
好像让一切停下是你的工作
The sun, the hard part of the night
太阳 夜晚难过的部分
The secret time when you wake To the sound of beating
你被敲门声吵醒的秘密时光
Rise to answer the door But he's not there
你起身去开门 但他不在门口
Because that sound is coming From inside you
因为那是你内心的声音
And you cannot answer it No matter how far in you go"
你无法去应答 哪怕你进入内心深处
"You loved him the way Fragile kids love gorgeous bullies
你就像脆弱的孩子 爱着帅气的霸凌者一样爱着他
-You wrote songs about him. You..." -[cymbals crash]
你写关于他的歌 你…” 我是说…
"You wrote poems about him
“你写关于他的诗
You still write poems about him You're writing one right now"
你还在写关于他的诗 你现在就在写一首”
[man] Why're you so sad? You're just so sad.
你为什么这么难过？你太难过了
Just something happier, for a change, might be nice.
换点高兴的东西可能会更好
I think everyone agrees. Get the singer back.
我想大家都同意 换歌手回来唱歌吧
[stuttering] Sorry. I just... I lost my place.
抱歉 我只是…我忘记读到哪了
It'll just take a second to find where I was.
我要花点时间看我读到哪了
[Joe] I can't stand seeing this. I'm sorry. I just can't.
我看不下去了 对不起 我就是不能
It's obvious what you are. You're blind with love.
你是什么情况很明显 你被爱蒙蔽了双眼
And what you love, writing, this city, your friends,
你爱的东西 写作、这个城市、你的朋友们
most of all, men like Benji,
最重要的是 像本吉那样的男人
what all those have in common is they will never love you back.
所有这些的共同点就是 他们永远不会也爱你
While you give everything.
而你却付出所有
It's crazy the lengths we go. We're a lot alike, Beck.
我们都这么全力以赴 真疯狂 我们很像 贝可
Last of the true romantics.
最后的真爱
[homeless man] ♪ Engine Engine number nine ♪
机头 在纽约运输线上的
♪ On the New York transit line... ♪
九号机头…
[Joe] I was considering this with my new friend,
我正跟我的新朋友“无家可归的 疯子先生”思考这个问题时
when the second luckiest thing this week happened.
这周第二件最幸运的事发生了
Could it really be?
这是真的吗？
It feels like I'm dreaming.
感觉像是在做梦
I'm not.
不是做梦
Beck, you're too drunk to be alone.
贝可 你太醉了 不能独自一人
What if some sicko had followed you down here?
要是有变态跟踪你到这里怎么办？
And you're too wasted to be standing so close to the tracks.
你太醉了 不能离轨道站得这么近
Beck! Beck, stop texting that arrogant club-soda, no-show dickhead.
贝可！别再给那个自大的 卖苏打水、放你鸽子的混蛋发短信了
♪ If my train jump off the track ♪
要是我的火车脱轨了
[Joe] You want Benji.
你想要本吉
You need Benji. You hold that phone like it is Benji,
你需要本吉 你抓着那手机 好像它就是本吉一样
'cause it's your only means to stay connected.
因为那是你唯一能跟他联系的方式
Forget Benji.
忘了本吉吧
And to hell with that phone.
去他的手机吧
[homeless man] ♪ Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up... ♪
捡起来！
♪ Engine, engine number nine ♪
机头 在纽约运输线路上的
♪ On the New York transit line... ♪
九号机头
Hey! Hey!
嘿！
You okay? Are you all right? Can you stand up?
你还好吗？你没事吧？ 你能站起来吗？
Just stay still.
别动
Half that shit down there can electrocute you, all right,
碰一下那东西就会让你触电的 好了
so just give me your hand.
把手给我
[homeless man] ♪ Pick it up! Pick it up! ♪
捡起来！
Sir, please, shut up!
先生 拜托 别唱了！
Give me your hand.
把手给我
Train's coming.
地铁要来了
♪ Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up! Pick it up! ♪
捡起来！
Your hand! Now!
你的手！快！
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I am so sorry. -Whoo.
我的天 太对不起了
No, it's fine. It's fine.
不 没关系
I, uh, hated... I hated this jacket. Ugh.
我本来就讨厌…我讨厌这件外套
-I really am sorry. -It's okay.
-真的很抱歉 -没事
You mind?
可以吗？
Sure, um...
当然
You know what? Let's get you in a cab. All right?
我帮你叫辆出租车 好吗？
I'm not always like this.
我并不总是这样的
I figured you had some kind of night.
我猜你今晚不太顺心
Some kind of.
算是吧
Hey, I don't want to sound like a stalker, but...
嘿 我不想听上去 像个跟踪狂 但是…
I think I know you.
我想我认识你
Oh, the... Right. [chuckles] Of course.
那个…对 当然认识
I remember. I'm sorry.
我想起来了 真抱歉
This is what I look like when I'm sober and have my hair up.
这是我清醒时 把头发扎起来的样子
Yeah. No, I... I remember.
对 不 我记得
It's okay, I have a pretty bland face.
没事 我长着一张大众脸
No, you don't.
不 不是的
Yeah, uh, Desperate Characters. I remember.
对 《绝望的人们》我记得
Yeah.
对
Where are you headed?
你要去哪？
Village. You anywhere close?
格林威治村 你顺路吗？
Ride with me. It's the least I can do.
跟我一起搭车吧 这是我起码能做的
Okay.
好的
Did you move here to be something? I did. But it's not working out.
你来这里是想作出一番成就吗？ 我是的 但不行
And I'm just running around 18 hours a day. Why?
我一天要连轴转18个小时 为什么？
Oh, God! Never mind. Sorry.
天啊！算了吧 对不起
No, please. I feel the same way sometimes.
不 请别这样 我有时候也这么觉得
This guy I know, he owns the bookstore.
我认识个开书店的人
He once told me that all books add up to one essential truth.
他有一次告诉我说 所有的书都证明了一个真理
Which is, if your IQ is above a certain number...
就是如果你的智商 超过了某一个数值…
life is pretty much unbearable. And the number is not even that high.
生活就非常难以忍受了 而且那个数值都不是很高
How'd you know I write poetry?
你怎么知道我写诗？
Doesn't every young writer in New York?
哪个在纽约的年轻作家不写呢？
I mean, I read a lot of poetry.
我读过很多诗歌
Who do you like?
你喜欢谁？
Strand, Sexton, Merrill...
斯特兰德、塞克斯顿、梅里尔…
You're describing my nightstand.
这些正是我放在床头柜上的
[scoffs] Well, if you read them to get to sleep every night,
如果你每晚都要读他们的诗入睡
then you definitely belong here.
你绝对属于这里
-What was your last name again? -Goldberg.
-你姓什么来着？ -戈登伯格
Where did you come from, Joe Goldberg?
你是哪里人 乔伊戈登伯格？
I grew up here.
我在这里长大的
I left for a little while. Chasing a girl.
我离开过一阵子 去追一个女孩
-But you came back? -Yeah, I missed it.
-但你回来了？ -是的 我想念这里
And I'm not a good chaser.
我也不擅长追人
Oh, this is, uh... This is me.
我到了
Thank you for sobering me up.
谢谢你让我清醒过来
And for saving my life.
还有谢谢你救了我
No, I didn't... I didn't save your life.
不 我没有救你
Yeah, you did.
有 你救了我
Oh, God.
天啊
[Joe] Of course.
当然了
-Benji. -[Beck] Hi.
-是本吉 -嗨
I... I fell on the tracks. It was crazy.
我跌倒掉到了铁轨上 太疯狂了
Babe, I told you people are basically good.
宝贝 我跟你说过这世上还是好人多
It's a great job, bro.
干得好 兄弟
[Joe] "Bro." You waste of hair.
“兄弟” 你这个长发男
Okay. Beck, it's freezing out here.
好了 贝可 这里很冷
-Wait. Maybe I can get your info... -Yeah. Um...
-等等 也许你可以给我留个联系… -好
Shit!
该死！
My phone!
我的手机！
-I must've dropped it in the subway. -Oh.
我一定是把它落在地铁上了
for when you get a replacement.
等你有新手机我们就能联系了
I'm basically enslaved to e-mail.
我主要是发邮件
[Joe] I get it. Smart. I'm practically a stranger. Can't be too careful.
我懂 聪明 我其实就是个陌生人 怎么小心都不为过
Okay.
好的
It's BeckInRealLife@gmail.com
地址是“贝可的真实人生” 发到谷歌邮箱
"Beck in real life."
“贝可的真实人生”
Thank you.
谢谢
[Joe] Here's what I learned this week.
-这就是我这周了解到的 -抱歉我没赶到
[Joe] You are special. You're talented. You're passionate.
你很特别 你有才华 你有激情
You're smart.
你很聪明
Except in the ways you are really not. Like not locking your phone.
只是在有些方面 你真的不聪明 像是你不锁手机
And falling for men like Benji. You know better, but you can't stop.
还有爱上像本吉这种男人 你更清楚 但你停不下来
Because, well, because everyone needs someone.
因为 每个人都需要另一个人
What you really need is someone to save you.
你真正需要的是找个人拯救你
I can help, Beck. Let me help you.
我能帮忙 贝可 让我帮你
[Paco] Joe.
乔伊
Pac. Hey.
帕克 嘿
What's going on? What're you doing out here?
怎么了？你在这里干什么？
It's Ron.
是罗恩
He came home drunk.
他喝醉了回到家里
He started yelling.
开始叫喊
Saying I thought I was smart,
说我自以为很聪明
reading my books and looking at him like he's dumb.
读我的书 把他看成一个笨蛋
What happened? Did he hurt you?
怎么了？他伤害你了吗？
No, he didn't touch me.
不 他没有碰我
I tried to stop him...
我努力想阻止他…
-I'm sorry. -Paco.
-对不起 -帕克
Paco, it's okay. Really. It's okay.
帕克 没事 真的 没事的
You know what? Come with me. We can fix this together. All right?
跟我来吧 我们能处理好的 好吗？
So, the first step to fixing something
解决问题的第一步
is to know no matter how destroyed it seems, it can always be saved.
就是要知道 不管破损看上去 有多严重 都是能补救好的
Books are no exception. You got it?
书也不例外 你明白吗？
Got it.
明白
So what we have here is a lying press. Basically just a huge clamp.
这有一台印机 其实就是个巨大的夹钳
Polyvinyl-acetate glue,
聚醋酸乙烯酯胶水
means no acid to burn the pages. Got your needle, thread,
意思是不会有酸烧坏书页 这里有针、线
and finally, right out of Bugs Bunny...
最后 还有兔八哥那里弄来的…
a trusty mallet.
可靠的锤子
You see this?
看到这个了吗？
We don't need this.
我们不需要这个
[Benji] Johno! Listen to this.
乔诺！听听这个
"Dear Benji, heard about your soda.
“亲爱的本吉 我听说了你的汽水
Am interested in including you on my fall list of must-tries.
有兴趣将你的产品 纳入秋季必须要尝试的清单中
Would love to discuss. Perhaps even try some? Jeff Pevensey."
想跟你聊聊 也许试喝一下？ 杰夫佩文西”
That's the dude you're always retweeting?
是你一直在转发他推特的那个人吗？
It's the culture guy from New York magazine.
他是《纽约》杂志的编辑
Hit him back, bro.
回复他啊 兄弟
No shit. Back off while I think.
当然 我得想好怎么回复他 别烦我
Jeff, comma, so nice to hear from you, bud, period.
杰夫 逗号 收到你的短信很高兴 兄弟 句号
Yeah, our sodas are legit, period.
对 我们的汽水超赞 句号
I would love to meet up to have you try the goods, period.
我想跟你见面让你试喝一下 句号
Let's set something up.
让我们安排一下吧
Scrape carefully along the spine.
顺着书脊小心地刮
Of course, you've got to watch your fingers.
当然 你也要小心别刮到手指
"Sounds great. I can call between meetings to see if you're available."
“听上去不错 我可以在会议的空档 给你电话看你有没有空”
This is gonna take us next level.
这会让我们更上一层楼
What time do you think we'll meet?
我们什么时候能见他？
No offense, we discussed this.
无意冒犯 我们讨论过的
It's best if the product has one clear face at the beginning.
在初期 产品还是让一个人 来介绍比较好
That's just more me.
让我来更合适
[Joe] Okay, the spine is sewn.
好 书脊缝好了
So you take this, pull it as tight as you can, that way.
你拿着这个 尽可能拉紧 那边
Yeah. That's it.
对 就是这样
Jeff!
杰夫！
The glue is set. We've applied the binder.
胶水涂好了 我们装订好了
Now...
现在…
you gotta be precise, and use exactly the force needed.
你要很精准 力道也要恰到好处
Hey!
嘿！
Hey, man. Jeff. Nice to meet you, man.
嘿 伙计 杰夫 很高兴见到你 伙计
Nice to meet you, too. Have you been here before?
我也很高兴见到你 你之前来过这里吗？
It's a... Not a lot of people know about it yet.
这是个…还没有很多人知道这里
It's an incredible after-hours. Very exclusive.
这是个很棒的业余休闲的地方 非常隐蔽
Yeah, I've been here a couple of times.
对 我来过几次
-Yeah? -Hmm.
是吗？
So you'll feel right at home, then.
那你会觉得像在家里一样
Please, after you.
你先请
All right.
好的
It's just down. To the left.
往下走就行了 向左拐
Hey, man, I'm thinking maybe...
嘿 伙计 我在想也许…
[Joe] It's 2:00 p.m. when the door chimes, and I'm ready.
门被推开时是下午2点 我准备好了
You told your girlfriends you'd come by. I know this because I have your phone.
你跟你的女朋友们说你会过来 我知道 因为你的手机在我这里
-I'll be back. -[Joe] Okay.
-我过会儿回来 -好的
Hey.
嘿
Remember me? From almost dying on the train tracks? [chuckles]
记得我吗？差点死在地铁铁轨上的？
Uh, it rings a bell. Hang on. Hang on.
我要想想 等等
I wanted to say thank you.
我想对你说声谢谢
No. You already did that.
不 你已经说过了
Well, uh, thanks again. [chuckles]
再次谢谢你
And I'm sorry for, uh, running off the other night.
我很抱歉那晚匆匆就离开了
-You had a guest. -Hardly.
-你有客人 -不算
So, I got you a present.
我有礼物要送给你
No, please. You don't have to get me anything.
不 请别这样 你不用给我买任何东西
Shut up and just look at it.
别说了 看看吧
"Engine, engine number nine On the New York transit line
“机头 纽约运输线路上的九号机头
If your girl falls on the track Pick her up, pick her up, pick her up"
如果你的女孩跌落在铁轨上 扶她起来”
[Joe] We already have in-jokes.
我们已经有只有我们俩才懂的笑话了
So...
那么…
anyway, that. And I better--
总之 礼物你收到了 我最好…
Maybe if you're not too busy, we could get a drink sometime?
也许你要是不太忙的话 我们能找个时候喝一杯？
Sure.
当然可以
Ugh. But I still can't find my phone.
但我还是没找到我的手机
I know. E-mail.
我知道 发邮件吧
That's right.
没错
See ya, Joe.
再见 乔伊
See you soon, Beck.
希望尽快看到你 贝可
Well played, sir.
干得漂亮 先生
Well played.
干得漂亮
[Joe] I'm not always right. I'm human. I make mistakes.
我并不总是对的 我是人 会犯错
You'll see.
你们会看到的
I have to check on a shipment downstairs.
我得下楼去检查一批书
-Can you watch the register? -Yeah.
-你能看着收银机吗？ -可以
[Joe] Hell, maybe I'm just a fool in love...
见鬼 也许我就是个 坠入爱河的傻瓜…
but I'm right about you,
但我看你看得很准
and I'm going to help you get the life you deserve, Beck.
我要帮你过上 你应该过上的生活 贝可
Please.
求你了
Whatever you think I did, you got the wrong guy.
不管你觉得我做了什么事 你找错人了
No.
不
I don't.
我没有